<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="198,284,575,241">Acknowledgments</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,344,1404,305">I would like to thank, with particular gratefulness, my friend and senior</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,394,1427,355">editor Victoria (Vicki) Austin for her assistance in copy editing. Without</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,440,1409,401">her, this book might not have reached its full potential. With her patient</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,490,1434,447">guidance and valuable and constructive suggestions, she helped me bring.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,536,711,497">this book up to a higher level!</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,621,790,582">How This Book is Organized</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,681,1414,646">The book you hold in your hands follows the spiral curriculum teaching</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,733,1388,692">approach, a method proposed in 1960 by Jerome Bruner, an American</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,782,1446,738">psychologist. According to this method, as a subject is being taught, basic</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,827,1402,788">ideas are revisited at intervals- -at a more sophisticated level each time-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,875,1462,836">until the reader achieves a complete understanding of the subject. First, the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,921,1444,885">reader learns the basic elements without worrying about the details. Later,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,969,1446,935">more details are taught and basic elements are mentioned again and again,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1022,1160,979">eventually being stored in the brain's long term memory.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1079,1317,1040">According to Jerome Bruner, learning requires the student's active.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="217,1125,1370,1093">participation, experimentation, exploration, and discovery.This book</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1176,1464,1134">contains many examples, most of which can be practically performed. This</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="213,1226,1444,1182">gives the reader the opportunity to get his or her hands on C# and become</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1272,956,1235">capable of creating his or her own programs.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1352,788,1313">Who Should Buy This Book?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1416,1418,1377">Thoroughly revised for the latest version of C#, this book explains basic</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1467,1448,1428">concepts in a clear and explicit way that takes very seriously one thing for</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1517,1391,1474">granted-that the reader knows nothing about computer programming..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="217,1574,1335,1535">Addressed to anyone who has no prior programming knowledge or.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1622,1439,1584">experience, but a desire to learn programming with C#, it teaches the first</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1671,1427,1632">thing that every novice programmer needs to learn, which is Algorithmic</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1714,1501,1678">Thinking. Algorithmic Thinking involves more than just learning code. It is a</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1767,1215,1728">problem-solving process that involves learning how to code..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1822,1418,1785">This edition contains all the popular features of the previous edition and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="217,1870,1432,1838">adds a significant number of exercises, as well as extensive revisions and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1923,1425,1884">updates. Apart from C# 's arrays, it now also covers dictionaries, while a</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1966,1462,1934">brand new section provides an effective introduction to the next field that a</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
