<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,339,1231,307">Fortunately, modern SQL databases allow us full control over them through</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,378,1233,346">data management systems and syntax.Through SQL we can create and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,417,1233,385">manage databases that contain anywhere from, say, twenty data items to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,454,1231,422">thousands.But before we go into the technical details, you need to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,493,1231,461">understand what a database is,what types there are,and how a data</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,532,1231,497">management system works.If you already know the basics and you're</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,568,1231,539">interested only in pure SQL,feel free to skip to the second chapter right</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="233,607,322,578">away.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,662,603,630">What's aDatabase?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,720,1231,688">The meaning of the term has changed over time from the days when people</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,756,1231,726">defined a database as a collection of data objects inside a list, to nowadays</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,798,1231,765">when we look at it as a repository of structured records that we can access</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,834,1233,804">through a management system and SQL.Take note that when we talk about</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,871,871,841">records, we refer to a data item's representation.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,924,1229,894">What does that mean? Imagine a business that keeps track of all their data.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,965,1231,933">Each record can represent a client, and the record will contain all of the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1004,1213,972">client's attributes like their ID, address, phone number, and similar details.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,1056,1231,1024">However, a database isn't meant only for conventional data we work with</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1095,1231,1063">directly. It also stores metadata.This type of data contains information</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1132,1231,1102">about the data in our database and tells us how it's structured.This is a</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1171,1231,1141">crucial aspect because without this information, it would be much harder to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1210,1229,1178">gain access to our data and change it as needed. In more technical terms,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1247,1229,1217">this means an SQL database is self-describing because it tells us everything</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,1286,1231,1251">we need to know regarding the relations between the data items inside and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="238,1322,1231,1293">what theyre made of. We can find the metadata in a data dictionary.The</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1359,1201,1329">data dictionary is used to describe all elements that make up the database.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1416,1231,1384">Databases come in all shapes and sizes depending on their purpose, but</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,1455,938,1423">generally we can place them all into three categories:</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="374,1506,1229,1474">1.The smallest and simplest type of database is the Persona</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="397,1547,1231,1515">Database.It's used to store a user's information, doesn't contain</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="397,1584,1210,1554">vast numbers of data items, and the structure has a basic form.</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
