<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="153,156,344,119">Starting with C++</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,255,1056,208">What will you find in this chapter?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="157,308,1332,276">Since this book is a hands-on book, it contains code that you can type, compile, and run. To</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,339,1281,312">compile the code, you will need a C++ compiler and linker, and in this book that means</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,374,1277,347">Visual Studio 2017 Community Edition, which provides Visual C++. This compiler was</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,411,1294,384">chosen because it is a free download, it is compliant with C++ standards and it has very</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="157,445,1271,418">wide range of tools to make writing code easier.Visual C++ provides C++11-compliant</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,484,1304,451">language features and almost all the language features of C++14 and C++17.Visual C++ is</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,515,1296,486">also provided with the C99 runtime library, C++11 standard library, and C++14 standard</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="153,551,1320,521">library. All of this mentions of standard means that the code that you learn to write in this</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,584,889,557">book will compile with all other standard C++ compilers.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="161,642,1251,615">This chapter will start with details about how to obtain and install Visual Studio 2017</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,681,1326,654">Community Edition.If you already have a C++ compiler, you can skip this section.Most of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,715,1328,688">this book is vendor-neutral about the compiler and linker tools, but Chapter 10, Diagnostics</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,754,1338,721">and Debugging, which covers debugging and diagnostics, will cover some Microsoft-specific</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="157,787,1251,760">features.Visual Studio has a fully featured code editor, so even if you do not use it to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="153,825,928,791">manage your projects, you'll find it useful to edit your code.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,879,1300,852">After we've described the installation, you'll learn the basics of C++:how source files and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,920,1292,887">projects are structured, and how you can manage projects with potentially thousands of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="152,948,220,922">files.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,1010,1320,980">Finally, the chapter will finish with a step-by-step structured example. Here you will learn</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="157,1043,1271,1016">how to write simple functions that use the standard C++ library and one mechanism to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="157,1082,501,1055">manage files in the project.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,1209,507,1168">What is C++?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,1263,1287,1236">The predecessor of C++ is C, which was designed by Dennis Richie at Bell Labs and first</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,1303,1302,1271">released in 1973. C is a widely used language and was used to write the early versions of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="159,1334,1263,1307">Unix and Windows. Indeed, the libraries and software-development libraries of many</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,1373,1340,1340">operating systems are still written to have C interfaces. C is powerful because it can be used</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,1406,1230,1379">to write code that is compiled to a compact form, it uses a static type system (so the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="153,1442,1281,1411">compiler does the work of type checking), and the types and structures of the language</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="155,1479,891,1446">allow for direct memory access to computer architecture.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="719,1724,787,1687">[8]</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
