<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="472,657,1318,601">about the cover illustration</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,753,1316,727">The figure on the cover of The Design of Web APIs is captioned "Girl from Drnis,Dalma-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,790,1316,763">tia, Croatia.The illustration is taken from a reproduction of an album of Croatian tra-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,827,1316,800">ditional costumes from the mid-nineteenth century by Nikola Arsenovic, published by</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,861,1316,836">the Ethnographic Museum in Split, Croatia, in 2003.The illustrations were obtained</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,900,1316,873">from a helpful librarian at the Ethnographic Museum in Split, itself situated in the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,935,1316,910">Roman core of the medieval center of the town: the ruins of Emperor Diocletian's</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,971,1318,944">retirement palace from around AD 304.The book includes finely colored illustrations</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,1008,1314,981">of figures from different regions of Croatia, accompanied by descriptions of the cos</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="282,1043,603,1017">tumes and of everyday life.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="317,1079,1316,1054">Dress codes and lifestyles have changed over the last 200 years, and the diversity by</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,1116,1316,1089">region, so rich at the time, has faded away.It's now hard to tell apart the inhabitants</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,1152,1316,1125">of different continents, let alone of different hamlets or towns separated by only a</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="278,1189,1314,1158">few miles. Perhaps we have traded cultural diversity for a more varied personal life-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,1224,1316,1197">certainly for a more varied and fast-paced technological life. Manning celebrates the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,1260,1316,1233">inventiveness and initiative of the computer business with book covers based on the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="284,1297,1316,1270">rich diversity of regional life of two centuries ago, brought back to life by illustrations</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="280,1330,809,1307">from old books and collections like this one.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="726,1690,774,1661">IIXX</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
