<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="154,100,207,69">xvii</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="638,98,812,73">ABOUT THIS BOOK</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="294,173,1291,146">Chapter 4 introduces the OpenAPI Specification and demonstrates how to describe</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,210,1185,183">an API in a structured and standard way using such an API description format.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,247,1291,220">Part 2 focuses on how to design don't make me think APIs that will be easy to under-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,281,517,256">stand and easy to use.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,318,1291,293">Chapter 5 explains how to design straightforward data representations, error and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,355,1291,328">success feedback, and flows of API calls that people will understand instantly and use</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,391,328,364">easily.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,428,1291,401">Chapter 6 teaches how to design even more easy-to-understand and easy-to-use APIs,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,464,1293,436">whose users (humans or machines) will be able to guess how APIs work, by making</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,499,805,474">them consistent, adaptable,and discoverable.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,536,1291,509">Chapter 7 shows how to organize and size all aspects of APIs in order to keep them</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="256,572,676,543">easy to understand and easy to use.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="290,605,1289,578">Part 3 shows that API designers must take into account the whole context surround</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,644,1156,617">ing an API and the whole context surrounding the API design process itself.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,680,1047,653">Chapter 8 describes API security and how to design secure APIs.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,717,1293,690">Chapter 9 teaches how to modify an API without unduly impacting its users, and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,752,1293,725">when and how to version it. It also demonstrates how to design APIs that will be easy to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,786,586,763">evolve from the ground up.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="290,825,1052,798">Chapter 10 focuses on how to design network-efficient web APIs</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,859,1293,834">Chapter 11 exposes the whole context that API designers must take into account</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="259,896,1291,871">when designing APIs. It comprises adapting communication mechanisms (request/</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,933,1293,906">responses, asynchronous, events, and batch or bulk processing)evaluating and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,969,1293,942">adapting to consumers' or providers' limitations, and choosing an adequate API style</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="261,1004,691,979">(resource-,function-or data-based).</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="290,1044,1294,1012">Chapter 12 explains how API designers participate in the creation of different types</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,1079,1294,1048">of API documentation, taking advantage of an API description format like the OpenAPI</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="256,1114,430,1085">Specification.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="292,1149,1289,1122">Chapter 13 shows how API designers can participate in the growing of many APIs by</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,1189,1294,1154">participating along the whole API lifecycle and across many APIs. It especially focuses</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,1220,755,1193">on API design guidelines and API reviews.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="290,1255,1287,1231">This book should be read from cover to cover, each chapter in order. Each new chap.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,1293,1291,1268">ter expands what has been learned in previous ones.That being said, once you have fin-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="253,1332,1294,1301">ished chapters 1, 2,and 3, you can jump to any chapter covering a topic that you need</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="253,1368,526,1337">to investigate urgently.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,1426,486,1399">About the code</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="255,1474,1291,1451">This book contains many examples of source code both in numbered listings and in</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,1513,1289,1488">line with normal text.In both cases,source code is formatted in a fixed-width font</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,1549,1289,1522">1ike this to separate it from ordinary text.Sometimes code is also in bold to high-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="259,1586,1293,1559">light code that has changed from previous steps in the chapter, such as when a new</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="257,1623,726,1596">feature adds to an existing line of code</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
