<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="834,257,999,218">CHAPTER 3</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="525,343,998,292">Layered Architecture</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,701,999,673">The most common architecture style is the layered architecture</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,735,998,709">otherwise known as the n-tier architecture. This style is the de facto</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,772,999,746">standard for most applications because it aligns with traditional IT</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,806,999,780">team structures where teams are organized by technical domains</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="202,842,999,816">(such as presentation teams, backend development teams, database</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,876,997,851">teams, and so on).Because it is so widely known by most archi-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,915,1001,881">tects, designers, and developers, the layered architecture is a natural</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,951,1001,919">choice for most business application development efforts. However,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,982,1001,956">like all architecture styles, it has its strengths and weaknesses and is</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,1018,632,992">not always suitable for some systems.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1104,398,1062">Description</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1159,1001,1125">Components within the layered architecture style are organized</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1194,1001,1162">into horizontal layers, each performing a specific role within the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1228,1001,1198">application (such as presentation logic, business logic, persistence</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,1262,1001,1236">logic, and so on).Although the number of layers may vary, most</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1297,1001,1268">layered architectures consist of four standard layers: presentation,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1333,1001,1303">business, persistence, and database (see Figure 3-1). In some cases,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1367,999,1341">the business layer and persistence layer are combined into a single</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1402,999,1373">business layer, particularly when the persistence logic (such as SQL)</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1436,999,1410">is embedded within the business layer components. Thus, smaller</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1508,930,1481">complex business applications may contain five or more layers.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="975,1686,1003,1659">15</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
