<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="836,257,1001,218">CHAPTER4</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="433,335,998,291">Microkernel Architecture</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,699,994,675">The microkernel architecture style is a flexible and extensible archi</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,737,999,711">tecture that allows a developer or end user to easily add additional</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,772,1003,746">functionality and features to an existing application in the form of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="195,808,1001,778">extensions, or "plug-ins, without impacting the core functionality</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,840,998,816">of the system. For this reason, the microkernel architecture is some-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,876,1001,851">times referred to as a "plug-in architecture'(another common name</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,911,999,885">for this architecture style). This architecture style is a natural fit for</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,947,996,921">product-based applications (ones that are packaged and made avail</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,984,1001,953">able for download in versions as a typical third-party product), but</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="195,1018,1001,988">is also common for custom internal business applications. In fact,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1056,1001,1020">many operating systems implement the microkernel architecture</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1086,682,1059">style, hence the origin of this style's name</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="193,1177,362,1129">Topology</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,1224,996,1198">The microkernel architecture style consists of two types of architec-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,1262,999,1236">ture components: a core system and plug-in modules. Application</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1296,999,1269">logic is divided between independent plug-in modules and the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="195,1335,1001,1299">basic core system, providing extensibility, flexibility, and isolation</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="199,1365,994,1339">of application features and custom processing logic.Figure 4-1 illus</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="195,1404,919,1371">trates the basic topology of the microkernel architecture style.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1453,1001,1423">The core system of this architecture style can vary significantly in</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1489,999,1462">terms of the functionality it provides.Traditionally, the core system</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1522,996,1496">contains only the minimal functionality required to make the sys</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="201,1558,998,1532">tem operational such as the case with older IDEs such as Eclipse),</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="197,1590,999,1568">but it can also be more full featured such as with web browsers</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="975,1688,1003,1659">25</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
