<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,266,460,211">Objective</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,325,1481,286">Chapter 1 is all about the basics of Unity. You'll be downloading the Unity</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,374,1488,335">tools and creating your first project. You'll learn about the different parts of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="208,424,1488,380">the editor, where you'll create your first objects and add some simple</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,470,1478,431">Physics. By the end, you'll have written your first Scripts and hooked up</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,520,1150,481">some basic Input for changing the rotation of an object.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,578,1483,539">Chapter 1 will give you both a strong understanding of the basics, a firm</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,621,1277,589">roadmap for what comes next, and a simple demo to build upon</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="213,743,861,692">Unity: The Broad Strokes.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,807,1485,768">Unity is one of the leading game engines, used by both independent and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="217,850,1481,818">AAA Developers throughout the world.It can be used to make games for</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,903,1485,864">PC, Mac, mobile devices, consoles, and is the leading choice for VR/AR</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,997,940,960">for almost any hardware platform out there.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1059,1483,1020">As for the toolset, Unity's Editor is where you'll be spending most of your</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1107,1483,1068">time. It allows you to quickly put together scenes, test gameplay in real</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1157,1462,1118">time, and even pause your game if you need to debug a session in progress.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1212,1166,1173">The robustness of the toolset is - in a word - phenomenal.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1272,1483,1238">Coding is done using C#, a language that resembles C++, only a bit less</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1325,1485,1286">complex (doesn't require header files, built in message handling, etc.). C#</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1370,1485,1332">can also be compiled, helping it to run faster than most other scripting</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1421,1483,1382">languages, and has its own memory manager so you don't have to worry</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1464,924,1430">about allocating and deallocating memory.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1524,1483,1487">To write our code, we will be utilizing Visual Studio, which comes built-in</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1572,587,1538">when we install Unity..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1634,1483,1597">The Unity Hub Is another important piece of the unity ecosystem. Here you</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1684,1483,1645">can manage different versions of Unity, browse and download your</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="208,1735,1127,1691">projects, and collaborate with others in the community.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1792,954,1753">In fact, the Hub is where our journey begins.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1909,610,1861">Installing Unity</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
