<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,195,1243,170">&gt;&gt; Scheduling: Making the use of resources fair to all concerned is another way</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="424,264,1258,239">timing lights at intersections are no longer simple devices that count down the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="424,297,1229,272">seconds between light changes.Modern devices consider all sorts of issues,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="424,331,1093,304">such as the time of day, weather conditions, and flow of traffic.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,380,1254,355">&gt;&gt;Graph analysis:Deciding on the shortest path between two points finds all sorts</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="423,414,1227,385">of uses.For example, in a routing problem, your GPS couldn't function without</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="424,447,1252,422">this particular algorithm because it could never direct you along city streets using</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="424,482,1246,455">the shortest route from point A to point B.And even then, your GPS might direct</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="421,513,1149,488">you to drive intoa lake(https://theweek.com/articles/464674/8-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="423,547,1029,522">drivers-who-blindly-followed-gps-into-disaster).</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,597,1254,570">&gt;&gt; Cryptography:Keeping data safe is an ongoing battle with hackers constantly</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="424,630,1254,605">attacking data sources.Algorithms make it possible to analyze data, put it into</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="422,663,1070,638">some other form, and then return it to its original form later.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="421,746,1198,721">varied. You start at the same place; perform the same steps, in the same</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="422,779,1216,755">manner, every time you play.Without the capability to generate seemingly.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="423,813,1074,788">random numbers,many computer tasks become impossible.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,888,1300,861">This list presents an incredibly short overview.People use algorithms for many</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,921,1300,896">different tasks and in many different ways, and constantly create new algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,956,1300,929">to solve both existing problems and new problems. The most important issue to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="240,991,334,969">REMEMBER</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,989,1298,964">consider when working with algorithms is that given a particular input, you</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1019,1300,994">should expect a specific output. Secondary issues include how many resources the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1054,1298,1029">algorithm requires to perform its task and how long it takes to complete the task.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1087,1300,1062">Depending on the kind of issue and the sort of algorithm used, you may also need</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1120,901,1097">to consider issues of accuracy and consistency.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1226,1031,1181">Finding algorithms everywhere</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1278,1298,1253">The previous section mentions the toast algorithm for a specific reason.For some</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1314,1300,1287">reason, making toast is probably the most popular algorithm ever created.Many</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1347,1300,1320">grade-school children write their equivalent of the toast algorithm long before</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1380,1300,1355">they can even solve the most basic math. It's not hard to imagine how many</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1414,1302,1388">variations of the toast algorithm exist and what the precise output is of each of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1445,1298,1420">them.The results likely vary by individual and the level of creativity employed.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1480,1300,1455">There are also websites dedicated to telling children about algorithms, such as the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1515,1298,1490">one at https://www.idtech.com/blog/algorithms-for-kids.In short, algo-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1545,1079,1520">rithms appear in great variety and often in unexpected places..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="156,1756,196,1725">14</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="230,1754,705,1729">PART 1 Getting Started with Algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
