<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,193,1314,168">sequencing the human genome were possible in our age because scientists found</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,231,1318,204">algorithms that run fast enough to complete the task.Measuring which algorithm</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,262,1318,237">is better in a given situation, or in an average usage situation, is really serious</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="378,299,1079,268">stuff and is a topic of discussion among computer scientists.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,364,1318,337">When it comes to computer science, the same algorithm can have multiple</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,397,1316,370">presentations; why do it one way when you can invent multiple methods just for</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,432,1316,405">fun? For example, you can present the Euclidean algorithm in both recursive and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,462,1314,437">iterative forms,asexplainedathttp://cs.stackexchange.com/questions/1447/</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="378,497,1319,468">what-is-most-efficient-for-gcd. In short,algorithms present a method of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,528,1314,505">solving formulas, but it would be a mistake to say that just one acceptable algo-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,565,1318,538">rithm exists for any given formula or that only one acceptable presentation of an</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,597,1316,570">algorithm exists. Using algorithms to solve problems of various sorts has a long</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,632,987,605">history - it isn't something that has just happened.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,698,1314,671">Even if you limit your gaze to computer science, data science, artificial intelli-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,732,1316,705">gence, and other technical areas, you find many kinds of algorithms - too many</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,763,1314,738">for a single book. For example,The Art of Computer Programming, by Donald</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,798,1316,771">E. Knuth (Addison-Wesley)spans 3,168 pages in four volumes seehttp://</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,829,1316,804">www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/0321751043/datacservip0f-20/)and still</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,863,1314,836">doesn't manage to cover the topic (the author intended to write more volumes)</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,898,1081,871">However, here are some interesting uses for you to consider:</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="399,967,1287,942">&gt;&gt; Searching:Locating information or verifying that the information you see is the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="438,1004,1231,977">information you want is an essential task.Without this ability, you couldn't</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="442,1037,1269,1010">perform many tasks online, such as finding the website on the Internet selling</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="440,1104,1271,1077">shown by Google's recent change in its algorithm (https://www.youaretech</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="440,1137,1275,1110">com/blog/2021/1/26/webpage-experience-a-major-google-a1gorithm-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="436,1168,693,1143">update-in-2021nbsp).</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="399,1218,1262,1193">&gt;&gt; Sorting:Determining which order to use to present information is important</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="438,1251,1231,1228">because most people today suffer from information overload, and putting</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="436,1283,1252,1260">information in order is one way to reduce the onrush of data. Imagine going</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="438,1318,1254,1293">to Amazon,finding that more than a thousand coffee pots are for sale there,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="440,1353,1214,1328">and yet not being able to sort them in order of price or the most positive</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="440,1384,1262,1359">review.Moreover,many complex algorithms require data in the proper order</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="438,1418,1237,1393">to work dependably, so ordering is an important requisite for solving more</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="442,1451,549,1430">problems.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="399,1503,1245,1476">&gt;&gt;Transforming: Converting one sort of data to another sort of data is critical</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="438,1536,1208,1511">to understanding and using the data effectively.For example, you might</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="440,1569,1218,1544">understand imperial weights just fine, but all your sources use the metric</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="442,1603,1260,1578">system.Converting between the two systems helps you understand the data</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="824,1754,1246,1729">CHAPTER 1 Introducing Algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="1279,1758,1319,1727">13</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
