<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,193,1298,168">The third section of the chapter discusses algorithms in a real-world manner, that</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,229,1300,204">is, by viewing the terminologies used to understand algorithms and to present</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,264,1296,237">algorithms in a way that shows that the real world is often less than perfect.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,297,1300,270">Understanding how to describe an algorithm in a realistic manner also helps to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,331,1287,304">temper expectations to reflect the realities of what an algorithm can actually do.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,395,1300,370">The final section of the chapter discusses data.The algorithms you work with</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,430,1300,405">in this book require data input in a specific form, which sometimes means</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,462,1300,437">changing the data to match the algorithm's requirements.Data manipulation</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,497,1300,470">doesn't change the content of the data.Instead, it changes the presentation and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,530,1302,505">form of the data so that an algorithm can help you see new patterns that weren't</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,565,1102,538">apparent before (but were actually present in the data all along)</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="163,698,743,651">Describing Algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,780,1298,753">Even though people have solved algorithms manually for thousands of years,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,813,1294,788">doing so can consume huge amounts of time and require many numeric computa-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,846,1300,821">tions, depending on the complexity of the problem you want to solve.Algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="361,881,1302,852">are all about finding solutions, and the speedier and easier, the better. A huge gap</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,913,1300,888">exists between mathematical algorithms historically created by geniuses of their</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,948,1298,921">time,such as Euclid (https://www.britannica.com/biography/Euclid-Greek-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="361,977,1298,956">mathematician),Sir Isaac Newton (https://www.britannica.com/biography/</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1014,1298,987">Isaac-Newton),or Carl Friedrich Gauss (https://www.britannica.com/biography/</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1046,1300,1021">Car1-Friedrich-Gauss),and modern algorithms created in universities as well</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1079,1300,1054">as private research and development laboratories.The main reason for this gap is</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1147,1294,1122">priate algorithm speeds up the task significantly.You may notice that more prob-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1181,1300,1154">lem solutions appear quickly today, in part, because computer power is both cheap</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1212,668,1189">and constantly increasing.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1282,1300,1255">When working with algorithms,you consider the inputs, desired outputs, and the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1314,1300,1287">process (a sequence of actions) used to obtain a desired output from a given input.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="363,1384,1300,1353">way because you haven't really considered how they work in a real-world setting..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1445,1300,1420">Sources of information about algorithms often present them in a way that proves</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1478,1296,1453">confusing because they're too sophisticated or even downright incorrect.Although</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="367,1515,1300,1488">you may find other definitions, this book uses the following definitions for terms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="365,1547,999,1522">that people often confuse with algorithms (but aren't):</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="154,1756,194,1725">10</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="230,1754,705,1729">PART 1 Getting Started with Algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
