<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,195,1316,170">Every task you perform on a computer involves algorithms. Some algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,231,1316,204">appear as part of the computer hardware. The very act of booting a computer</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="378,266,1318,235">involves the use of an algorithm.You also find algorithms in operating systems,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,297,1316,272">applications, and every other piece of software.Even users rely on algorithms.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,330,1318,304">Scripts help direct users to perform tasks in a specific way, but those same steps</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,362,1314,335">could appear as written instructions or as part of an organizational policy</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,393,507,370">statement.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,462,1316,437">Daily routines often devolve into algorithms. Think about how you spend your</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,497,1316,470">day. If you're like most people, you perform essentially the same tasks every day</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,532,1318,505">in the same order, making your day an algorithm that solves the problem of how</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,565,1316,538">to live successfully while expending the least amount of energy possible.After all,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,595,939,570">that's what a routine does; it makes us efficient.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,661,1256,634">Throughout this book, you see the same three elements for every algorithm</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="376,728,682,700">1.Describe the problem.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,777,421,746">2.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="434,777,1062,754">Create a series of steps to solve the problem (well defined).</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="179,966,1123,911">Using Computers to Solve Problems</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1046,1316,1019">The term computer sounds quite technical and possibly a bit overwhelming to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1081,1314,1054">some people, but people today are neck deep (possibly even deeper) in computers.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="378,1114,1316,1085">You wear at least one computer, your smartphone, most of the time. If you have</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1147,1318,1120">any sort of special device, such as a pacemaker, it also includes a computer. A car</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1181,1318,1154">can contain as many as 150 computers in the form of embedded microprocessors</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,1212,1318,1187">that regulate fuel consumption, engine combustion, transmission, steering, and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1245,1314,1218">stability (see https://spectrum.ieee.org/software-eating-car for details)</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,1282,1316,1255">provide Advanced Driver-Assist Systems (ADAS), and more lines of code than a jet</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,1314,1316,1287">fighter.A computer exists to solve problems quickly and with less effort than</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="380,1347,1317,1318">solving them manually. Consequently, it shouldn't surprise you that this book</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1382,1168,1355">uses still more computers to help you understand algorithms better.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="384,1445,1316,1420">Computers vary in a number of ways.The computer in a watch is quite small; the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1515,1318,1488">smaller computers all tasked to work together to solve complex issues, such as</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1547,1316,1520">predicting tomorrow's weather. The most complex algorithms rely on special</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1580,1319,1555">computer functionality to obtain solutions to the issues people design them to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="382,1613,1316,1588">solve.Yes,you could use lesser resources to perform the task, but the trade-off is</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="378,1648,1319,1619">waiting a lot longer for an answer, or getting an answer that lacks sufficient</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="824,1756,1248,1729">CHAPTER 1 Introducing Algorithms</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="1273,1756,1318,1727">15</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
