<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,195,1456,163">learned and subsequently taught to others. The only difference between</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,241,1456,210">those who excel and those of mediocre achievement is that one group has</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,285,1287,256">1earned a thinking methodology that has not occurred to the other.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,331,1454,297">With this hypothesis, it is my understanding that the people who</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,378,1456,344">developed the program went to the South Pacific and sought out those</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,422,1422,390">who demonstrated an ability to walk over hot coals with their bare feet</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,465,1456,434">without any physical damage whatsoever. Upon finding a few of these South</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,512,1459,473">Pacific "fire-walkers," the program developers proceeded to analyze their</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,558,1459,519">beliefs and attitudes so as to arrive at a thinking methodology they could</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,599,662,565">teach in the United States..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="268,648,1456,604">I'm sure I don't have to point out the physical and emotional</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,687,1454,653">implications of attempting to walk over a red-hot bed of coals with your</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,780,1427,746">normally be overwhelming. The potential physical damage to your feet-</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,826,1454,787">with the possibility of being crippled for the rest of your life- -is quite real.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,870,1456,836">And yet, as presented by several news organizations, both television and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,919,1459,875">print, people from all walks of life involved in the seminar accomplished</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,958,1459,923">what we would universally agree to be a tremendous feat. They overcame</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1004,1068,970">their fear and walked 20 feet over a bed of hot coals.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,1048,1456,1014">Now, I'm not going to have you fire-walking the futures pit, but habits of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1092,1459,1060">thought die hard. And to make way for the new thinking methodology I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1138,1459,1104">offer as a means of excelling as a trader, you will have to question some of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1182,1451,1148">your beliefs and probe deeply rooted concepts of what is possible.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1228,1456,1194">Sometimes only a thorough mental "house cleaning" can help you throw</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1277,1459,1235">away failure to make room for success. And exposing yourself to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1316,1456,1282">information that may cause you to ask yourself "what if it were true" is the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1362,900,1328">first step to any mental cleansing process..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1406,1459,1372">For many reasons, which will be explored in greater depth in Part II, it</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1450,1456,1418">rarely, if ever, occurs to the beginning trader that the markets confront him</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1496,1459,1462">with an environment that is categorically different from anything he is</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1537,1454,1503">accustomed to or trained to deal with effectively by society. For example.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1586,1451,1547">the markets can be looked at as a never-ending event, always changing.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1630,1454,1596">virtually without structure, in perpetual motion, with an unlimited potential</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1674,858,1640">for profit as well as loss in every trade..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,1723,1459,1684">The psychological impact on the individual interacting with such an</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1766,1456,1732">environment is formidable especially when you consider the many ways</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1813,1456,1779">in which all of us typically go about structuring our lives with highly defined</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1857,1459,1822">boundaries, limits, and rules, so things stay basically the same. For most</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1905,1461,1861">people, a static environment is a fundamental component of their sense of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,1947,625,1908">security and well-being..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,1991,1454,1956">Not only can the markets destroy a person's sense of security by forcing</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2032,1459,2000">the trader to confront, on a moment-to-moment basis, his lack of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2081,1461,2047">acceptance of change, but they also produce an emotional environment of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2125,1459,2090">considerable competitiveness and stress. There's the compulsive need to win</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2168,1456,2137">millions, with the simultaneous fear of financial devastation. The markets</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="829,2237,866,2205">25</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
