<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,195,1055,163">selection of which skills should be used and when.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="266,246,1461,202">I do not offer a trading system in this book. It's more a means of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,292,1461,248">interfacing a trading system with the mind's psychological structure. If a</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,334,1456,300">trading system provides awareness of market signals, and suggests behaviors</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,383,1459,339">appropriate for any given market situation, then the thinking methodology I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,422,1311,390">will share with you teaches skills and processes of skill application.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,468,1459,434">Havingtheskillsnecessary to consciously manipulateone's</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,514,1456,480">psychological environment is essential for the trader who recognizes how</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,558,1456,524">ineffectual a trading system can suddenly become whenever a tense</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,602,918,568">situation demands a split-second decision.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,646,1456,614">Most everyone reading a book of this nature would consider himself as</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,692,1456,658">successful to one degree or another, either through trial and error, or the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,733,1454,699">rigorous application of some proven formula, through which each has</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,782,1456,748">learned intentionally or not skills or methodologies of thought to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,823,568,792">achieve this success..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,867,1454,833">In any case, we all have a natural tendency not only to want to achieve</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,916,1456,882">success in something, but also to apply the principles of success that work</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,960,1456,923">very well in one situation to practically everything else. It often doesn't</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1006,1459,972">occur to us that some environments may require very different</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1050,927,1016">psychological resources to achieve success.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1096,1456,1062">Suppose, for example, that you arbitrarily tried to apply a certain thought</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1140,1456,1106">system of success to trading futures or stocks without first investigating the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1184,1456,1150">usefulness or validity of that system in relationship to the actual conditions</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1230,1461,1191">as they exist in the markets. More than likely, you would be doomed to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1274,731,1240">failure before you even started.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1318,1454,1284">Obviously people don't consciously start trading with the belief that they</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1364,1459,1325">don't have the right resources or that they're going to fail. In fact, it is just</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1408,1454,1374">the opposite. Because most traders come from or still enjoy very successful</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1457,1459,1413">careers outside of trading, they have a great deal of confidence in their</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1498,1456,1464">ability to extend this success in the trading environment. This unfounded</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1542,1459,1508">confidence, coupled with the way the markets distort a person's concept of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1586,1459,1554">reward in relationship to time and effort expended, will cause the trader to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1632,1459,1598">form some very unrealistic expectations about the kind of results he should</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1674,369,1640">achieve.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,1718,1449,1689">Believing that trading is easy is the reason for the unrealistic expectations</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1766,1456,1732">And they are probably the single biggest reason why most traders never</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1810,1459,1779">make it beyond the initial levels of development before they lose all their</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1854,355,1825">money.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1900,1456,1866">Starting out believing that trading is easy is a psychological trap that</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1944,1454,1910">entices almost all traders. But it isn't too difficult to understand why, when</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1991,1459,1956">you examine the dynamics of the process of how we set up a standard of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2039,1456,1998">performance for ourselves by which to gauge our progress. There are four</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,2125,617,2088">expectations for results.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="271,2173,1459,2132">First is our basic concept of time; most people believe that it is limited,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="829,2237,866,2205">29</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
