<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,195,1454,163">small amounts, because, at that time, it felt as if the market was insulting</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,244,1432,210">me by offering such paltry sums compared to what I needed or expected.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="271,292,1456,248">As my financial problems grew, so did my desperation. And I certainly</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,375,1456,344">to the belief that I could trade out of these difficulties. That is until March</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,419,1456,390">1982; by then it was all over. A mere eight months after moving to Chicago</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,468,1461,429">to pursue my dreams of financial independence, I had nothing left except</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,512,1043,475">my job, apartment, clothes, a television, and a bed..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,556,1451,521">Practically overnight, almost all the symbols that validated my identity</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,602,1451,568">were gone. What I mean is, a big part of my self-concept was made up of my</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,646,1454,612">possessions like my house, my car, and especially my credit. Maintaining</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,690,1456,655">flawless credit was something I had always been proud of. Now I found</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,736,1459,702">myself without any of these things. As I've already pointed out, it's not as</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,780,1456,746">if there hadn't been plenty of evidence to suggest the possibility of this</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,826,1459,787">happening, because there had been. But there was a part of me that</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,870,1454,831">wouldn't allow a direct confrontation with this evidence or the implications.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,916,1459,877">It was just too easy to make excuses for all the things going on around me</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,955,527,921">that didn't add up..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,1006,1456,965">Refusing to confront or consider the implications of all the conflicting</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1048,1456,1014">information created a great deal of stress. And to compound the situation, I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1092,1456,1057">had this intense fear that I would lose everything. But again, I did</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1138,1456,1104">everything possible to hide this fear and put it somewhere in my mind</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1182,1456,1148">where I couldn't feel it. Yet, there must have been a part of me that sensed</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1226,1456,1194">my impending fall. Why else would I have been so consumed with fear?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1272,1459,1233">But how could I face any of this when I had no way of reconciling the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1313,1454,1279">imbalance that losing all of these things would create? What I mean is the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1360,1459,1325">imbalance between what I believed about myself and the things that</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1403,1400,1372">validated these beliefs. Who would I be after all these things were gone?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1450,1456,1416">Well it didn't take me very long to find out. As my financial condition</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1540,1456,1506">down. I eventually accepted the inevitability of doing what I believed was</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1584,1077,1547">the ultimate act of failure and filed for bankruptcy..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1628,1456,1593">There were a lot of things that changed inside of me as a result of this</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1674,1456,1640">experience. And like any one else forced to deal with major changes in his</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1720,1456,1686">or her life, I learned a lot about myself. The first thing that happened, which</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1764,1459,1730">was quite surprising, was that the stress dissipated. Actually I was</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1813,1456,1771">overcome with a great sense of relief with nothing to anticipate, dread, or try</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1852,1454,1820">so desperately to defend against. I was living through my worst fear and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1898,1456,1859">found there really wasn't anything about the situation that I couldn't deal</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1942,1456,1908">with. It wasn't nearly as bad in reality as I imagined it would be. I was still</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1988,1459,1952">alive and healthy, I was able to think and function, and I started to appreciate</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2032,868,2000">my ability to think as my greatest asset..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,2081,1461,2039">This sense of appreciation began to grow into a deeper level of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2122,1459,2088">understanding about the basic nature of my identity. For the most part, I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,2171,1459,2127">grew up believing that who I was consisted of the things that I owned. The</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="829,2239,866,2205">20</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
