<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,197,1456,163">created them. You can think of it this way: none of us has the mental</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,244,1451,210">capacity to be aware of everything going on in the environment at once.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,288,1454,253">The environmental information we focus our attention on, out of all that</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,331,1459,300">exists, will be the information that has the most importance to us. As we</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,375,1454,344">allocate more and more of our attention to certain kinds of information,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,419,1454,387">because of its importance, we are at the same time systematically excluding</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,463,1454,429">other types of information from our awareness. I created my losses instead</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,512,1208,478">of avoiding them simply because I was trying to avoid them.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="271,560,1459,519">Instead of being positively focused on market information that would</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,602,1459,563">indicate the potential for opportunity, I was more concerned with</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,646,1459,612">information that validated what I feared the most. As a result, a great deal of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,692,1459,653">market information pertaining to other possibilities and opportunities that</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,780,1454,746">by. The only way I could have perceived these opportunities (other than</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,821,1459,792">after the fact) would have been to let go of whatever was causing me to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,870,1409,836">divert my attention away from what was happening in the market "now."</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="271,914,1456,880">I had no way of knowing what I was missing out on until my beliefs</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,960,1459,921">about the significance of losses and being wrong started changing. Once</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1004,1456,970">this shift in perspective occurred, I started to notice behavior characteristics</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1048,1459,1014">of the market and relationships between those characteristics that I was</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1092,718,1060">otherwise totally oblivious to.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="278,1138,1459,1104">At some point, I realized that because I had already lost everything, I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1182,1456,1148">really didn't have anything to fear, and, as a result, I inadvertently learned</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1228,1459,1194">one of the most important lessons to becoming a successful trader: how to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1272,1456,1238">'accept" a loss without any negative consequences. No guilt, anger, shame,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1316,551,1282">or self-punishment.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1360,1459,1328">As my fear of losing dissipated, I was seeing and experiencing a different</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1406,1451,1372">market because I was different. It was as if someone had removed blinders.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1450,1456,1416">which I didn't know existed, from my eyes. Up till then, my trading had</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1494,1456,1462">always been affected by my fears.I didn't have the slightest notion of what</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,1540,1456,1503">it would be like to trade without fear or that doing it was even a possibility</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1584,1205,1550">and least of all, that it was, in fact, necessary to be successful.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,1632,1464,1591">What also became very apparent to me was the extent to which all of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1674,1459,1640">my fears had effectively blocked me from understanding why it was so</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1718,1456,1686">absolutely necessary to have some clearly defined trading and money</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1764,1451,1730">management rules that must be followed. It was all starting to make sense.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1808,1459,1774">The more I followed my rules the more I trusted myself. The more I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1854,1459,1815">trusted myself the more I could focus my attention on subtle relationships</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1898,1456,1864">in the market's behavior to learn new things about the market helping me</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1942,1456,1908">become a better trader. Eventually I could gauge the positive effects these</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1993,1459,1952">new attitudes had on my ability to shift my perspective and flow with the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,2032,1459,2000">markets. The less I cared about whether or not I was wrong, the clearer</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2073,1456,2044">things became, making it much easier to move in and out of positions,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2122,1459,2088">cutting my losses short to make myself mentally available to take the next</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2168,438,2134">opportunity.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="829,2239,866,2205">22</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
