<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,197,1456,163">more possessions I owned, the more of a person it made me. What I began</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,241,1456,210">to realize is that I was more than the things I had accumulated.When the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,288,1454,253">facade was stripped away, it allowed me to sense this deeper dimension</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,336,1459,292">that, up to this point, I had only the slightest inkling of These new</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,378,1456,344">awarenesses, in turn, helped me understand how being wrong and losing</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,422,1459,390">something didn't in any way diminish me as a person. I was beginning to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,463,1459,431">learn that there was a certain freedom in granting myself permission to be</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,514,1459,475">wrong and maybe there was no such thing as a failure, unless something</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,556,1087,521">positive and useful isn't learned from the experience.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="268,604,1461,560">However, I didn't relate these personal experiences because I thought</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,646,1456,612">they were particularly unusual, except for one. Everyone knows there are</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,692,1459,655">many traders who lose everything they own, and even though some of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,733,1454,702">them will come to the same kind of awarenesses about themselves, they</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,780,1456,746">wouldn't necessarily be able to do it as a trader, considering the financial</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,826,1449,792">requirements. I, too, was not in a financial position to keep on trading</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,870,1456,836">except that I still had my job at Merrill Lynch. In fact, for me it was</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,914,1459,880">business as usual, as if nothing at all had happened. I certainly wasn't</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,958,1456,923">about to announce to my customers or anyone in the office that I had</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1004,1456,970">just filed for bankruptcy. My job as an account executive was one of the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1048,1456,1014">few things I had left, and as far as I was concerned, it depended on me</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1094,556,1060">being a good trader.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1135,1454,1101">This is the one key difference for me that ultimately lead to the creation</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1179,1456,1148">of this book. I was fortunate enough to be able to keep on trading (although</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1272,1456,1238">taking place, putting me in a unique position to examine and study the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="229,1318,1459,1279">various ways in which the condition of my inner psychological</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1362,1451,1328">environment affected what I experienced in the outer physical environment.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1406,1456,1372">This relationship between inner and outer isn't always that apparent but in</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1494,1454,1459">an opportunity to profit from price movement, and these opportunities are</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1540,1454,1506">basically in perpetual motion. It is an environment where the individual</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1584,1456,1550">has the freedom to create his own results, unimpeded by many of the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1630,1456,1596">constraints that exist in everyday social life. These never ending</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="239,1671,1449,1637">opportunities make the market a perfect mirror of the trader's attitude</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1715,1456,1684">What the trader sees in that movement and what he can do about it the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1762,1456,1730">markets have no control over. All the choices and all the power to turn</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1805,1252,1771">these choices into experience reside in the mind of each trader.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="276,1852,1456,1820">For example,if I perceived the market as a threat, afraid of what it might</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1898,1451,1864">take away from me, it wasn't because the outside conditions were actually</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1944,1456,1910">threatening me in some way. It became very apparent to me that my fear was</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,2037,1459,1993">appropriately served my best interests. It was only the lack of trust I had in</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2076,1242,2042">myself to do what needed to be done that I was really afraid of.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="271,2122,1459,2083">Furthermore, I discovered that my mental framework was structured to</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2166,1451,2132">avoid losses at all costs and in my desperate attempts to do so, I actually</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="826,2237,866,2205">21</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
