<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,195,1439,161">trading error before it actually happens. Other techniques or skills include</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="349,346,1055,314">focused on what you want-not what you fear.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="295,414,1459,373">2. Learning how to recognize the skills you need to progress as a trader</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="352,456,1459,422">and then stay focused on the development of those skills, instead of.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="352,502,1210,468">the money, which is merely a by-product of your skills</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="293,563,1459,524">3. Learning how to adapt yourself to respond to fundamental changes in</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="352,607,846,573">market conditions more readily.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="298,668,1454,633">4. Identifying the amount of risk you are comfortable with - your "risk.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="352,763,1461,721">consistent with your ability to maintain an objective perspective of.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="347,801,598,765">market activity.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="349,914,809,872">perception of an opportunity..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="298,967,1456,936">6.Learning how to let the market tell you how much is enough, instead</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="354,1016,1454,982">of assessing the potential from your personal value system of how.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="349,1060,605,1026">much is enough..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="295,1121,1461,1082">7. Learning how to structure your beliefs to control your perception of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="349,1162,645,1131">market movement.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="295,1226,1279,1191">8. Learning how to achieve and maintain a state of objectivity</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="298,1286,1454,1252">9. Learning how to recognize "true" intuitive information and then</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="354,1333,932,1299">learning how to act on it consistently</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="507,1481,1183,1447">HOW IS THIS DIFFERENT FROM</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="617,1533,1070,1498">A TRADING SYSTEM?</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1618,1459,1579">Trading systems give us a way to define, quantify, and categorize market</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1659,1456,1625">behavior. Since the markets offer traders a seemingly infinite combination of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,1708,1456,1674">behaviors, all with their corresponding opportunities and risks, it is easy</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1752,1456,1718">to understand how our minds can become overwhelmed. Trading systems</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="231,1793,1456,1762">limit the scope of market behavior, and therefore make this activity a little.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1842,1459,1808">easier for our minds to manage. They also give us direction and</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1891,1461,1849">suggestions about what to do in a given market situation. Without them</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1930,1459,1898">traders could easily feel as if they are floating aimlessly in an endless sea of</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,1976,1072,1942">possibilities and opportunities with no land in sight.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="273,2025,1456,1983">Since trading systems define opportunity and offer suggestions,</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2066,1459,2027">following these suggestions can lead to the development of skills, even</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2110,1456,2076">though as suggestions they merely point the way for your awareness to be</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="234,2156,1456,2117">directed. A true skill not only points the way, but almost automatically</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="236,2200,1459,2166">begins to direct awareness as well. And a thinking methodology controls the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="829,2239,866,2207">28</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
