<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<OBJECT>
  <HIDDENTEXT>
    <PAGECOLUMN>
      <REGION>
        <PARAGRAPH>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,330,825,284">1 Configuration and setup</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,440,1404,401">This first chapter is purely optional. If you already know how to build C.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,488,1409,451">code, especially if you're familiar with working at the command prompt.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,541,1485,500">stop wasting time and merrily skip up to chapter 2. Otherwise, slug it out and.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="252,630,1000,591">.Review the C language development cycle</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="252,699,1356,660">.Use an integrated development environment (IDE) to build code</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="254,770,1425,731">.Explore the excitement of command-line programming in a terminal.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="293,820,795,781">window, just like Grandpa did</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="259,880,1416,841">Review options for linking in libraries and supplying command-line</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="296,930,469,891">arguments</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1018,1404,979">The purpose of this material is for review, though if you've never used a</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1070,1344,1031">command line to program, you're in for a treat: I find command-line</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1118,1446,1079">programming to be fast and easy, specifically for the tiny programs created</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1164,1411,1128">in this book. This code is well suited for the command-line environment..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="217,1254,1293,1221">Still reading? Good. This chapter serves as a review when your C</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1311,1416,1265">programming skills are rusty or if you just want to confirm that what you</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1357,1321,1315">know is up to par for successfully navigating the rest of the book. I</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1412,1400,1364">appreciate that you're still here. Otherwise, these pages would be blank..</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1499,1328,1451">And why do skills get rusty? Is it the iron and oxygen? The field of.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1545,1448,1512">computer jargon needs to plant new terms for poor skills, something highly</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="215,1597,1464,1558">offensive and obnoxious to the point of being widely accepted. I'll ruminate</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1650,1444,1604">on the topic, and maybe add a quiz question along these lines at the end of.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="210,1693,405,1657">the chapter.</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="212,1833,878,1781">1.1 The C development cycle</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="217,1932,1372,1893">According to ancient Mesopotamian tablets currently on display in the</WORD>
          </LINE>
          <LINE>
            <WORD coords="208,1980,1391,1941">British Museum, four steps are taken to develop a C language program..</WORD>
          </LINE>
        </PARAGRAPH>
      </REGION>
    </PAGECOLUMN>
  </HIDDENTEXT>
</OBJECT>
